hello everybody welcome to become AI
hackathon
we'll give a minute to get some people
in here
[Music]
so it's generated by our internal
segment that was trained on kama
coloring kama correcting cityscapes cam
vids mapillary vista the same ones
everyone else cuz we just don't like oh
yeah my name is Jorge for those that
don't know youtubers so much now I'm
this sick hackathon food what we're
really here to do is induce as much FOMO
as possible so you'll tell all your
friends you know which I was at the
comic hackathon
that's a good plan fine tuning our shop
hello French onions gross ma'am what
happened to twitch things it's a new
year it's 2020 I am rehab check out the
kitty leaderboard it's pretty good for
that and I think it is that in video
paper
stall click somatic segmentation on the
videos result okay we got a bunch of
people here I'll show you guys the
secret TVs what's made available we're
not going to disturb them here are some
fun projects to work on
here is some random projects to work on
here are some open project pilot
projects to work on and here is our
Wi-Fi network
welcome to the common hackathon where we
have kickoff and dinner some challenges
will come live tomorrow you can see my
terrible handwriting dinner lunch
presentations and then say goodbye
how was flex are going oh yeah yeah some
some some common employees decided they
were to do flex raise their hand home
project
the board for all the haters who said
you can't do flex rate with a logic
analyzer and an FPGA oh oh yeah
this is leaked content guys welcome to
my office you know my office can
transceivers and a logic analyzer and
then hopefully that will allow us to
intercept the messages there's an Audi
q8 in the garage there's more lidar in
the comma is right now then there's ever
been in history there's actually three
lied arse in here
because there's two lidar is in the in
the Audi q8 yeah this is actually old
wrong this is the a4 one this is gonna
be easy
is it hard
oh man to the keyway have good drivers
system yeah but I don't need right 45
because all the traffic but a dinner
mess up go okay and I couldn't ride a
traffic jam assist I don't know it
didn't like or something goes to me but
it didn't mess up and you were on the
highway yes it was like an agar b5 did
you have to wheel to reset it or could
you oh you're the wheel aha yeah
all right I don't know what else to tell
you guys you know next year or next time
it won't even be next year make sure you
get invited to the combat AI hackathon
and you could be participating in all of
this fun yeah that's all we got bye-bye